INIM ANDREW ESIET

@ inimandrew@gmail.com

**** 07011903917

Onipanu - Lagos State, Nigeria.

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-inim-887a22178/

https://twitter.com/grapheneee



Website optimization

Technical Analysis

Software Best Practices and improvement

Search Engine Optimization

UX Documentation and architecture

Brand Management

Excellent work ethic

Flexible and Adaptable

Verbal and written communication

Complaint resolution

Excellent time management skills

Passion for customer satisfaction

Superior attention to detail

Self-motivated professional

Strong organizational skills

Excellent teamwork and collaboration

Task Prioritization

Accepts direction and coaching graciously

Can-do attitude

PERSONAL DETAILS

GitHub: https://github.com/inimandrew

Skype: live:inim.andrew

Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/graphene12



Music

Movies

Reading

Listening to Podcasts



OBJECTIVE

An intuitive, proactive and result driven Tech enthusiast with over 4 years of full-stack web experience of designing, building and maintaining front-end and backend systems for different clients using my skills in HTML, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, Vuejs etc. Currently looking forward to nurturing a career and constituting a team that embraces and contributes to the success and growth of a corporate organization which desires support and appreciates special skills, personal effort and smart work. To effectively and efficiently maximize my skill, talent and knowledge by taking advantages of opportunities that abound for maximum productivity.



PORTFOLIO

https://graphene12.gitlab.io/portfolio/



EDUCATION

University of Calabar, Cross-River State, Nigeria.

Mar. 2015 - April 2019.

B.Sc. (Hons.) Computer Science

Stella Maris College, Lagos State, Nigeria.

Sept. 2007 - April 2012.

WASSCE



EXPERIENCE

Natterbase Limited, Lagos.

Oct. 2020 - till date

Front-End Developer

Collaborate with UI/UX Engineer to build User Interface and Interactions.

Develop the UI/UX from scratch using Technologies such as Tailwindcss and Nuxtjs.

Bind U.I to Backend data.

FHI 360, Calabar

June 2020 - July 2020

Web Developer

I developed a digital assessment tool to help the Team on the field in gathering, organising and providing a detailed report on data.

Developed a system for uploading questions and sequencing the questions based on the various responses from the user.

Asked a series of questions to the user based on the sequence programmed at the backend

Submitted the responses at the end of the survey,

Calculated the risk score based on the magnitude of each response

Showed the risk score to the user

Revealed further recommendations for the users based on the risk score.

Provided detailed reporting of the responses submitted.

GlobalShoppers Solutions Limited, Enugu

Jan. 2020 - May 2020

Web Developer

I developed an Api-centric E-commerce website with the following functionalities

User registration, authentication and Authorization.

Provided endpoints to communicate with the android app (JumpQ) to purchase goods from the android app.

Implemented a payment network to accept payments for goods from users.

Provided endpoints with the desktop application to provide its antitheft functionality.

BigStack Technologies, Calabar.

Jan. 2020 - Dec. 2020

Senior Developer

Delivered and maintained scalable system architecture to support high availability internet site with various internal applications.

Collaborated on all stages of system development lifecycle. From requirements gathering to production releases and maintenance.

Authored code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches.



INTERNSHIP

Intern at Silicon River Ultra-Tech, Calabar, Cross-River State, Nigeria.

Oct. 2017 - April 2018

Collaborated with the Senior Software staff to provide new software solutions.

Contributed Ideas and suggestions in team meetings.



EXPERTISE

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, jQuery, Vue.Js, MySQL, Microsoft Office, PostgreSql, MongoDb, Node.Js, Bootstrap, TailwindCss, Git.



REFERENCE

Available on Request - ""